I'm here to protect you.
Protect? Or control?
Do as they say.
They'll figure out
they've made a mistake.
If anyone hurts you...
I can look after myself.
Relationships are impossible.
Edward's nice. The end.
The locker.
the Polaroid.
the anonymous phone number.
the voice in the end.
the damn auction.
Coyote isn't being held
by an agency.
Cossack's working alone.
- It's him.
- We have Cossack.
I want proof he's alive.
He is alive
for four...
five more days.
From what I hear.
the news is not good.
Our missing agent is
in the hands of the Russians.
where they intend to use him
to maximum effect.
We'll have
to lean out of Ukraine.
This could change the shape
of the entire conflict.
This isn't bad news. It's good.
So you think
you can still get him back?
Yes. We'll find him.
We'll get him back.
You do not make promises
you cannot keep.
Is it Poppy Lewis
or Poppy Cunningham?
Yeah. I am close. aren't I?
Fuck!
Good morning. good morning.
How are you. Samia?
How are you bearing up
under our. uh. burdens?
I'm fine.
How are you bearing up?
I spoke with. uh. Osman
yesterday.
It was nothing.
I needed some fresh air.
Cooped up in that hotel room
day and night.
So you went
all the way across town
to another hotel room?
I read a paper
you published in Addis.
"Humanitarian Consequences
of Sexual Violence
Against Women and Girls
as a Military Tactic."
It's a good paper.
Terrible title.
Women's bodies are
a battleground.
This paper almost got you
excluded from the negotiations.
So I. uh. I read it. and. uh--
- And what?
- It is accurate.
This is what is happening
in Khartoum.
all over the country.
I told my cousin this paper was
a reason for them to bring you.
He. like me.
is a reasonable man.
Not all men are monsters. Samia.
I know.
Your work is. uh...
so important.
Thank you.
So...
go out for fresh air again.
for any reason.
men in Khartoum will arrest
your family.
Your mother. your sisters.
These men.
they may not be reasonable men.
Do I make myself clear?
Good morning. Good morning.
Very good to see you.
Welcome. welcome.
Slow down. What did he say?
My mother and my sisters.
I can't even be speaking
to you right now.
You're okay.
You're still in London.
You're safe.
Nowhere is safe.
We need time.
Samia. keep your cool.
Do everything they ask you.
Let me think about this.
Let me work it out.
I'll call you back.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
I just need to get to work.
Listen. as a precaution.
I need you stay here today.
Precaution? What's up?
Nothing. I just need
to check some things.
What things?
Like that guy that spoke to me?
No. Yes.
I just need you to stay here.
It's fine.
Cool. Don't tell me.
Cool plan. You look into it.
You spy that shit out.
I'll just stay here.
Maybe read a book.
knit something.
And maybe sometime
in the future.
we can meet up someplace
that's a real place.
Poppy.
Listen. my daughter thinks
she could have been followed
yesterday. Can you keep an eye?
- She good?
- She's fine.
- You sure?
- I need you to make sure.
Done.
Valhalla appeared
in 2014 providing
"little green men"
for false flag ops
in the lead-up to the
Russian annexation of Crimea.
Volchok was an ex-KGB.
SVR officer who found himself
in Ukraine in the company
of highly-trained
Spetsnaz
Special Forces operators.
He formed his new unit outside
of the command and control
of the regular Army.
At first. Volchok's ambitions
echoed elements
inside the Russian state
who wanted a more aggressive.
imperial foreign policy.
- After Crimea.
Valhalla forces pour
into Syria. Libya and Iraq.
They're able
to succeed in theaters
where coalition forces
had failed.
They took Palmyra
from Islamic State in two weeks.
Only because
they didn't give a shit
about who was
or wasn't a civilian.
Right. Of course. accusations
of war crimes swiftly followed.
rumors
of neo-Nazi insignia.
etcetera. but--
and this is the genius of it--
all Valhalla units
are registered abroad.
So. legally. Russia has
zero responsibility.
They have become
a global mercenary force.
All right. how many troops
we talking about
worldwide. a hundred thousand?
Across this many theaters.
I mean. uh. they're so vast.
estimates are tough.
Brigade strength or above
in a dozen countries.
Belarus. Ukraine. Syria. Sudan.
Mozambique.
Central African Republic.
Mali. Libya. Venezuela.
Madagascar.
The list is big.
We're picking up tensions
between Russian high command
and Valhalla.
How do we exploit that?
It's only led Volchok
to become more
security-conscious and insular.
On his bases.
an unauthorized cell phone
is grounds for a death sentence.
Carried out by sledgehammer.
So the world's
most paranoid asshole.
trained by old KGB
in counterespionage
and surrounded by
his own fanatical private army
of Nazi mercenary thugs--
Great.
Who wants to give it a go?
We're working on something.
An asset we could deploy.
But he's not gonna want
to do it.
Smart.
I don't fucking blame him.
This is a joke. right?
- No.
In that case. no. No way.
No fucking way on Earth.
- Where do you want to live?
- Fuck you.
You like Hounslow. Alex.
Poky little safe house.
You can't go home.
What's the plan?
He only gets the safe house
for six months.
- Then what?
- All of this.
all you are describing--
this is your fault. not mine.
What if I said I could get you
an American passport?
I would say.
shove it up your ass.
But there is no point.
because it doesn't exist. right?
Alex.
- Oh. my God. You are doing this.
Help us.
and we'll get you. your mom
and your brother
all U.S. citizenship.
Go fuck your mother.
We'll even
throw in health care
in case your brother needs it.
- I'm waiting.
- For what?
For the "or" here.
For the fucking small print.
And. please.
for the love of God.
please don't lie.
Or...
- Or...
Or we send you to Belarus
and trade documents
through a back channel that
identify you as a CIA asset.
Thank you.
Thank you for being honest.
I'm offering you a way out.
Through the gift shop?
May I ask you a question?
Why lay it out like this?
- Like there is a choice?
- Listen.
To make you feel better?
You got me cornered here?
You.
You are trapped. too.
We're all in hell.
Not just me.
All of us.
You have five minutes.
Take it or leave it.
- No. neither.
- No?
I don't even think
I'd enjoy one.
- Okay. bye.
Viola. I will see you tomorrow.
- Yes. tomorrow.
- Okay. Mwah. Bye.
Tweaked my back
playing squash with Reza.
No. no. don't-don't worry.
Don't worry. Oh. thank you.
- Where do you want it?
- Oh. just in my office.
You can put it down anywhere.
Thanks.
Should we open up the box
and hide the bottles?
- Are we celebrating?
- Yeah.
I am going to Iran.
Reza phoned me yesterday.
No way.
Way.
Congrats.
- Thanks.
Oh. watch the back.
Yeah. it's-it's gonna be great.
I'm really looking forward
to it.
- What the fuck?
- Not a word.
Let's move.
- Who are you?
- Your dad said stay indoors.
Next time. listen and do what
you're told until it's safe.
Hi.
- Hey.
How's it going?
- Am I bugging you?
- No. No. not at all.
What can I do for you?
Do you want to go
on another run?
Henry needs to see you. Now.
You're both wanted
in Henry's office.
What's up?
Dad.
Suddenly. it was time.
It was now or never.
I was in play.
My family was in play.
Samia's. too.
I had one move left.
You have any idea
why Beijing field operatives
were surveilling
your daughter's college?
14:12 today.
someone closed distance on Poppy
like they were about
to run a kidnap.
Good thing our street team
was on deck. huh?
Dozer told us you asked her
to watch Poppy this morning.
Said you seemed concerned.
like you might know something.
Or feared it.
Start anywhere you like.
Twice in the past week.
I thought I was being followed.
But you didn't flag it.
I figured if I was. my follow
team would have picked it up.
When they didn't.
I assumed I could relax.
But if it's real...
...I think I know what it is.
Richardson was right.
There are secret negotiations
taking place in London.
Both sides meet daily
at 73 Kensington Park Gardens.
A mansion belonging
to Chinese national Eric Huang.
I don't know an exact agenda.
but talks are between
the military government
and rebel forces in Sudan.
Dr. Samia Zahir
is playing a role
as a geopolitical expert.
Samia's in London
under the pretext
of attending
an educational conference.
I ran into her by chance
a few days ago.
She told me she was here
on a university visa.
but the truth is. every morning.
she joins these discussions
- at the highest level.
- And you did your own digging
to find all this out?
Yes.
- Why?
Because I didn't buy her story.
It didn't add up.
- Why engage at all?
Why not just walk away
when you bump into someone
you knew downrange?
Because I believe
Samia Zahir
to be of enormous value.
And you want us to recruit her?
Yes.
I think we have to.
Who?
You?
I think I can.
But it is important to...
- Dr. Zahir arrived
in London on the 25th.
Five weeks. here.
under our noses.
we knew nothing about it?
We heard some chatter
from the Brits
via a back channel.
We were looking into it
but getting nowhere.
If this is true. the Chinese
have fucking aced this.
Well. they think so. too.
I see opportunity here.
Every station around the world.
they have us under the thumb.
Never make mistakes.
Langley would eat this up
with a spoon.
Martian really thinks
he can get her?
Well. we're currently running
the scenarios and evaluations.
but yes. he does.
Go get her.
Oh. bugger.
Fuck.
Um...
Hello. sorry. y-you don't.
uh. have a pump. do you?
You got a flat tire?
Yeah. it was fine
when I came in.
Maybe it's a slow puncture.
It's your lucky day.
- I've got one of these.
- Oh. you're kidding.
- Yeah.
- Do you mind if I...
- I-I don't actually know
- how to do it myself.
- Do you want to hold that?
Yeah. This is gone.
Oh.
- Was it him?
- It's all fine.
Someone's gonna come
and ask you a few questions.
then they're gonna take you
to your mom's.
Why don't you come around
for dinner later?
Okay.
Hey.
On the 19th at three o'clock.
on our way into the Incas
exhibit. we ran into a woman.
my old friend.
You didn't catch her name.
Do you need another hug?
No. I'm good.
I better go.
Good as new.
- Wow.
That is brilliant.
Thank you so much.
How can I repay you?
- I-I do have some--
- Don't go to Iran.
S-Sorry?
You heard.
Don't fucking go to Iran.
Excuse me?
Repeat after me:
- "I love my family."
- What?
- Say it.
- Why?
Fucking say it.
I-I love my family.
Do not tell anyone
about this conversation.
Nothing. Not a word.
Their lives depend on it.
I don't understand.
You're right.
You do not understand Tehran.
Don't try. Just obey.
Okay?
Now...
where are we not going?
Iran?
Good.
Have a good day.
Can't be easy to fuck around
on your husband in Sudan.
Takes guts.
She knows what she wants.
she takes risks.
She might need to see this
as saving herself.
not being saved.
How did she contact you
to tell you she was in London?
There was no way
for her to contact me.
Martian ran into Sami
outside the British Museum.
I was with my daughter.
on the way to see
an exhibition on the Incas.
Do operatives
often run into people
they knew under their alias?
Never.
It's rare. It does happen.
Are there protocols?
- Not really. no.
just close off
communication gently.
Gently?
The rule is.
don't arouse suspicion.
The plan was.
see her once more for lunch.
which I did three days later.
And that's when she told you
- about the negotiations.
- Yes.
Were you surprised?
- Surprised?
- Well.
she did betray state secrets
to you spontaneously
with no encouragement.
I'm just a teacher to her.
She still in love with you?
Why don't you ask her yourself?
Unless we fuck this up. that is.
But if you had to call it?
Yes.
Can we use that?
If I get the chance.
Don't get stuck
on the danger she's in.
make her feel
what she felt before.
She's not betraying her home.
Home is you.
She's coming home.
Thank you. That's helpful.
He's in love with her.
What?
I said. "He's in love with her."
He never made a secret of it.
- He told you that?
- Yeah. Everything.
From the first meeting
to the last.
Every step of the way.
What about when he broke it off?
He did what he had to do.
Why didn't he report contact
at the museum?
Mm. Martian is
an experienced operative.
The Agency give guys like that
a long leash.
Did he ever talk
about a future with Dr. Zahir?
She was married. I think
they both knew what it was.
Is it possible that your own
feelings for Martian
have blinded you to what's
going on with these two?
My own feelings?
Perhaps you wanted to believe
that it was over between them.
My relationship here is one
of professional proximity.
Martian tries to get everyone
to fall in love with him.
Oh. well. now I feel great
'cause he never
tried it with me.
You okay?
I'm fine.
I have some thoughts
about this approach.
I'd hope so.
Naomi's on her way. My office.
They have her under
house arrest in her hotel.
When she leaves. they go
with her everywhere she goes.
She attends
the negotiations daily.
Is there something
we could do en route?
Anything discrete we could use?
A kitchen. A bathroom...
The route's secure both ends
and in the middle.
Anything staged. they'll pick.
- Medical emergency?
Send in a hotel doctor?
Get her out of there?
We need something quiet
and everyday. Unsexy.
You said she entered the country
on a university visa?
Royal College countersigned her
application. That's her cover.
Attack the cover.
University's pissed.
She's skipping class.
- They vouched her travel.
- Fire off an email.
They'll pull her visa unless
she comes in to explain.
Bone-dry.
- And they can't come with her.
- She's a teacher.
Good. We run a jack-in-the-box.
- Quick word?
- Super quick.
I have to brief Langley
on Coyote and Dr. Zahir.
Are we sure about Martian
setting the hook?
- I take it you're not?
- It's his baby.
- Right.
- Well. should it be?
The flea-flicker depends
on his personal connection.
- Yeah. I know.
- But...?
My gut?
I have to go.
Listen. gut is good.
I trust yours.
Find something concrete
and bring it to me.
If we win here. it's big.
"After failing to reply
to your calls and messages...
attention that you have com...
you have not completed
minimum required seminar...
Your UNESCO-sponsored
visa arranged
on promise of attendance...
failure to respond...
being forced
to inform embassy...
...result in cancellation
of visa status."
I read it. it's nothing.
What do you mean it's nothing?
I've been skipping class the whole time.
Look i brought it to you. didn't i?
Haven't i done everything
you've asked of me?
You've done nothing i've asked.
From the beginning
you've been difficult...
Willful. disobedien.
Are you trying to get sent home?
What are you talking about?
I am here because i believe in this.
Can't you see what
i've put on the line here?
How hard i'm trying to
make these talks work?
It says you failed to reply.
I have a million missed calls.
What am i supposed to say to people?
I'm locked in my room?
Against my will?
Go see this guy.
Fix it.
- Hey. Poppy.
- What the actual fuck. Dad?
- I ordered us some Chinese.
- Mm.
Chinese. My favorite.
Maybe even a movie?
Something I was working on
has cropped up here in London.
Now I have a whole team
of people protecting us.
It's their job
to get ahead of anything.
They did.
It's a fire drill.
Nothing burned down.
Test complete.
How do you know
that I lied for you?
You haven't even asked me.
- Because I trust you.
- You trust me to lie.
And I did.
I really. I really lied. but...
I don't know
if I did a good job.
Hey. hey. hey. hey.
Hey. hey.
I got myself into trouble.
You got me out.
Because you did.
now everything's good.
Go me.
You should probably get that.
Simon.
Dr. Zahir has
made an appointment
to come in to meet
Mr. Kent-Jones at 10 a.m.
at the Royal College
tomorrow morning.
Understood.
Good news?
That'll be the Chinese.
"The Chinese" or "The Chinese"?
Glad someone finds this funny.
Was it pillow talk?
No. I think she was serious.
Do you think she's capable
of leaving her husband for you?
Maybe one day she'll ask.
If I said yes.
I think she would.
Do you want that to happen?
If my mission was over?
Yeah.
If it was a possibility. yes.
Do you want that to happen?
If my mission was over?
Sit him down.
Who the fuck is this?
- Some guy.
I'm from the trucking
company. Alexei Orekhov.
He's clean?
- Absolutely.
Wait here.
Please. do you know
how long i will here?
General Volchok will see you now.
Sit.
Who do you work for?
I work for the Babrujka
Haulage company.
In logistics and accounts.
You sound nervous.
Mm.
No.
I'm not nervous.
Why not?
So you've got something you
want to tell me and only me...
Sylvia. what did that email say?
A matter of a highly
delicate nature...
Well then...
Speak my very delicate friend.
What i'm about to
say could get me killed.
I don't need this part. This... pre-amble.
Say what you came
to say. Do it now.
You've been getting fucked.
By my boss.
For a lot of money.
50.243.500 roubles.
That's how much you were charged
by my company for diesel this year.
I use a lot of your trucks.
I aked for photo of the fuel
before and after each trip.
By my calculations we fuck
you by 25% every invoice...
Over two years...
... so far that's over $300.000.
So you came in here... to
tell me that your company.
you. have stolen a third
of a million dollars from me.
That takes some balls.
He looks like he dosen't
have them but he does. Huge.
I could chain you to a Jeep
and drive you around.
then give you to the dogs.
I came because...
I don't want that to happen.
I didn't want you finding out another way.
I can't sleep.
Plus you hate your boss. Am i right?
Why else would you put a gun to his head?
No. Oh God. Please.
Please. Please.
Please.
I just have to check something.
Why was it so important
to see me and only me.
We've never met.
You deal with a few of my officers.
I don't know who my boss has bribed.
Final answer?
Yes.
It's a pretty good answer.
Also. Most men piss their pants.
Where did you get these balls...
...bean counter?
Orekhov made contact
with Volchok 2 p.m. today.
Security was as expected.
The target was isolated
behind a physical
and digital wall
with only three people present.
One. an unidentified barber.
Two--
Wait. a barber?
Why does this guy need a barber?
He's fucking bald.
He's bald but he shaves
the rest once a week.
Barber's out.
we can't wait that long.
Two. a bodyguard.
the only person allowed
to get close who's armed.
Uh. Orekhov heard someone
call him "Sasha"?
Alexander Bulgov.
He's worked close security
for Volchok seven years.
Yeah. the man has literally
taken a bullet for him.
Who's the third?
- Uh. his secretary.
Orekhov heard him
call her "Sylviya."
Said they seemed close.
said she had two desks.
one outside
the general's office.
another inside. in a corner.
The secretary.
...this data needs
to be completed.
because once we get the rundown
- when we are in Iran...
- Mm-hmm.
...it will be too complicated.
All the calculations.
Which reminds me...
And we have
to talk about this as well.
'cause this is very complex.
Yeah. take a look at this.
It's my wife. Sorry.
Uh. hello?
Hey. bicycle man.
I'm so sorry. I've-I've. um.
I've got to take this.
Where is Isabel.
and what have you done to her?
I borrowed Isabel's phone.
My battery died.
She's very kind. Cute. too.
I got the feeling from her
you haven't changed
- your travel plans.
- Leave my wife alone.
If you go to Iran.
you'll die before you arrive.
This is not a threat.
I don't threaten. I inform.
Who are you?
I'm your horoscope.
What?
H-Hello? Hello?
Fuck.
Hey.
- Hello? Isa?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm fine. What's up?
- Where are you?
- The market.
I just helped this lovely man.
He bought us free chorizo
because I was such
a Good Samaritan and let him
- make a call on my phone.
- No. no. no. no. no. no.
No. no. no. no.
Don't-don't go near that guy.
Okay? D-Don't go near him.
Get... go straight to home.
Please. just-just trust me.
Do as I tell you.
He checks out.
Worked at the company ten years.
Had girlfriend but it never worked.
No kids.
You said he left the country
reacently. Why? For how long?
Couple of weeks.
He has a sick brother in Poland.
Cancer.
He went to see him because he
went into hospital for treatment.
So seems clean.
It tooks balls to do what he did.
But i don't believe him.
What do you mean?
Was he brave...
Or pretending to be brave.
He should have been
pretending to be brave. Instead...
He looked like he was
pretending to be scared.
But was brave.
And he didn't piss his pants.
I think...
This is our American friends...
Saying hello.
So. he told his boss
he's not going?
Had second thoughts.
Said his wife
didn't want to move to Iran.
He blamed his wife?
Brave guy.
So. does that mean
you're going instead now?
Few months? A year?
You know I can't tell you.
You shouldn't even know
where I'm going.
One question.
Straight yes or no.
Are we just fucking?
No.
But we could.
They will ask you
to justify your absence.
What will you tell them?
- I was busy setting up
the rescue of artifacts
from the museum in Khartoum
to safety with the International
Council of Museums
here in London.
Busy won't cut it.
I also asked someone
to record the seminars
and give me a copy.
I have been taking part.
They can test me.
And you'll pass?
I'll ace it.
They're on their way in.
Hi. I'm meeting
with Mr. Kent-Jones.
He's up on the fourth floor.
Thank you.
They're going up.
Clean. No microphones.
no transmitters.
Come in.
- Mr. Kent-Jones?
- Yes.
Take a seat. Mrs. Zahir. Please.
Thank you for seeing me.
I must offer my apologies
for having missed
so many seminars--
Excuse me for a moment.
Paul?
No.